//This object contains data regarding each question
const QUESTIONOBJ = [
    {
    question: 'What does the popular fitness term IIFYM stand for?',
    answers: {
      a: 'It Is For Your Mental',
      b: 'If It Fits Your Macros',
      c: "It Isn't Fun You Maniac", 
      d: "I'm In For Your Mind",
    },
    correctAnswer: ' "If It Fits Your Macros."',
    number: 1,
    value: 1,
    },
    {
    question: ' How many calories equate approximately to one pound of fat loss?',
    answers: {
      a: '1000',
      b: '1500',
      c: '2500', 
      d: '3500',
    },
    correctAnswer: ' "3500."',
    number: 2,
    value: 3,
    },
    {
    question: 'Which of the following metabolic pathways is largely responsible for providing your body with quick, intense energy up to ~10 seconds?',
    answers: {
      a: 'Cyclic AMP',
      b: 'AMP Kinase',
      c: 'ATP-PC', 
      d: 'Gluconeogenesis',
    },
    correctAnswer: ' "ATP-PC."',
    number: 3,
    value: 2,
    },
    {
    question: 'What is one advantage of HIIT training?',
    answers: {
      a: 'Burn maximum calories in minumum time',
      b: 'Burn a greater percentage of fat when compared to LISS',
      c: 'Low impact on the joints', 
      d: 'Keeps the heart rate steady' ,
    },
    correctAnswer: ' "Burn maximum calories in minumum time."',
    number: 4,
    value: 0,
    },
    {
    question: 'What are one of the benefits of long term fasting?',
    answers: {
      a: 'Increase in HGH',
      b: 'Increase in fat mobilization',
      c: 'Increase in fat oxidation', 
      d: 'All of the above',
    },
    correctAnswer: ' "All of the above."',
    number: 5,
    value: 3,
    },
    {
    question: 'Which of the following health benefits would result from regular walking?',
    answers: {
      a: 'Increased blood pressure',
      b: 'Decreased risk of CHD',
      c: 'Increased resting heart rate', 
      d: 'Decreased heart rate',
    },
    correctAnswer: ' "Decreased risk of CHD."',
    number: 6,
    value: 1,
    },
    {
    question: 'Which of the following is a long term adaptation to muscular strength training?',
    answers: {
      a: 'Increased size of type II muscle fibers',
      b: 'Decreased size of type II muscle fibers',
      c: 'Increased number of type II muscle fibers',
      d: 'Decreased number of type II muscle fibers',
    },
    correctAnswer: ' "Increased size of type II muscle fibers."',
    number: 7,
    value: 0, 
    },
    {
    question: 'What is the definition of muscular strength?',
    answers: {
      a: 'The ability of muscles to exert maximum force in one contraction',
      b: 'The ability of muscles to exert minimum force in one contraction', 
      c: 'The ability of muscles to repeatedly exert maximum force', 
      d: 'The ability of muscles to repeatedly exert minimum force',
    },
    correctAnswer: ' "The ability of muscles to exert maximum force in one contraction."',
    number: 8,
    value: 0,
    },
    {
    question: 'Which of the following would be classified as in the aerobic fitness zone?',
    answers: {
      a: '65% max heart rate',
      b: '75% max heart rate', 
      c: '85% max heart rate',
      d: '95% max heart rate',
    },
    correctAnswer: ' "75% max heart rate."',
    number: 9,
    value: 1,
    },
    {
    question: '"Which body type has broad shoulders and a muscular build?"',
    answers: {
      a: 'Ectomorph',
      b: 'Mesomorph',
      c: 'Endomorph', 
      d: 'Somatotype',
    },
    correctAnswer: ' "Mesomorph."',
    number: 10,
    value: 1,
    }
    ];
  
    //console.log(QUESTIONOBJ);